export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your experience with hearing voices?",
      "options": [
        "Never experienced+0",
        "Rarely or occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+3",
        "Constantly+2"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never experienced"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do the voices you hear typically have positive, neutral, or negative content?",
      "options": [
        "Positive+0",
        "Neutral+1",
        "Negative+3",
        "A mix of positive and negative+2"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you find it challenging to distinguish between the voices and external sounds?",
      "options": [
        "No challenges+0",
        "Slight challenges+1",
        "Moderate challenges+2",
        "Severe challenges+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "No challenges"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with auditory hallucinations or related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+0",
        "Considering it+1",
        "No, not yet+2",
        "No, and I don't plan to+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do the voices you hear impact your daily life and activities?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Low impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do the voices provide guidance or instructions, or are they more disruptive and distressing?",
      "options": [
        "Provide guidance+0",
        "Disruptive and distressing+1",
        "Varies+2",
        "Not applicable, as I don't hear voices+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Not applicable, as I don't hear voices"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your experience of hearing voices?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing issues related to hearing voices is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+0",
        "Agree+1",
        "Neutral+2",
        "Disagree+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been experiencing these auditory phenomena?",
      "options": [
        "A short period+0",
        "Several months+1",
        "Years+2",
        "I've never experienced hearing voices+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "I've never experienced hearing voices"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been experiencing these auditory phenomena?",
      "options": [
        "A short period+0",
        "Several months+1",
        "Years+2",
        "I've never experienced hearing voices+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "I've never experienced hearing voices"
    }
  ]
}
